{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulations."
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "test",
      "description": "test",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "Mock Deck 323423",
      "description": "MDS",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Differentiate between Real DOM and Virtuals DOM.",
      "back": "Virtual DOO updates are faster but do not directly update the HTMLSS",
      "id": 1,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "How do you pass data 'down' to a React child component?",
      "back": "As properties or propser",
      "id": 3,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>sssss",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL'ssssssyesssitworks",
      "id": 4,
      "deckId": "2"
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "test",
      "back": "testss",
      "id": 6,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "testsss",
      "back": "test",
      "id": 7,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "test 234",
      "back": "234344",
      "id": 9,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "456asdadad",
      "back": "test",
      "id": 10,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "1sajhdjkdnsajkndasjk",
      "back": "1",
      "id": 12,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "What has ears but cannot hear?",
      "back": "A cornfields",
      "id": 13,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "dasr",
      "id": 14,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "e",
      "back": "wer",
      "id": 15,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "dw",
      "back": "sdsdf",
      "id": 16,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "sd12378912379832",
      "back": "sdf",
      "id": 17,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "sdf",
      "back": "sdfdkfshjodkslfhjoklfn",
      "id": 18,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "hi ",
      "back": "hey s",
      "id": 19,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "sddsf",
      "back": "sdfdsfedited",
      "id": 20,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "yes",
      "back": "nop",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "ewre",
      "back": "werw",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "sdf",
      "back": "sdfnew",
      "id": 23,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "sdf",
      "back": "sdfsdfsdf",
      "id": 24,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "s",
      "back": "sds",
      "id": 25,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "adfsnew",
      "id": 26,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "dfsa",
      "back": "afdsafdsaf",
      "id": 27,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "wd",
      "back": "dwfsfd",
      "id": 28,
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "q",
      "back": "fw",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "front": "sdf",
      "back": "sdfsfdfsd",
      "id": 30,
      "deckId": "1"
    }
  ]
}